[
	{
		"question" : "I _______ the flat tire when I ______ the dent in my car door.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "changed, noticed" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "was changing, was noticing" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "was changing, noticed" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "changed, was noticing" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 2

	},
	{
		"question" : "She ______ her friends outside while she was studying in the library.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "seen" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "saw" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "seeing" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "was seeing" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 1

	},
	{
		"question" : "Yesterday was very cold.  People ______ heavy coats.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "wear" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "wore" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "wearing" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "were wearing" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 3
	
	},
	{
		"question" : "We ______ ready to leave when Kevin ______ his mind.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "getting, changed" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "got, changing" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "got, was changing" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "were getting, changed" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 3
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "While you ______ fun with your friends, I ______ at home all alone.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "were having, was sitting" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "having, sitting" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "had, was sitting" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "were having, sat" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 0
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "Before you ______ here, I ______ on the couch.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "were getting, was sitting" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "getting, sitting" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "were got, sat" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "got, was sitting" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 3
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "Kevin was up all night.  What ______ ? ",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "he was doing" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "was he doing" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "he did" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "did he do" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 1
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "Jean ______ at that restaurant ______ it closed.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "was working, was closing" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "worked, closed" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "working, closed" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "worked, closing" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 1
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "She ______ for Google after she ______ school.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "was working, was finishing" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "worked, finishing" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "worked, finished" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "working, finishing" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 2
		
	},
	{
		"question" : "The dogs ______ before I ______ in the door. I could hear them outside.",
		"answers" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "were barking, walked" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "barking, walking" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "barked, was walking" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "was barking, walked" }
			
		],
		"correct" : 0
		
	}
]